Rick Whitesell Record Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 3. 7" Discs, 3; 12 linear feet Boxes: 1 - 23 Folders: 3.7.1 - 3.7.1883
  - The Chordettes, Record Label:Cadence (Folder 365, Box 5)
    - Baby Of Mine, 1
    - Photographs, 2
  - The Chordettes, Record Label:Cadence (Folder 366, Box 5)
    - Theme From Goodbye Again, 1
    - The Exodus Song, 2
  - The Chordettes, Record Label:Cadence (Folder 367, Box 5)
    - Faraway Star, 1
    - Never On Sunday, 2
  - The Chordettes, Record Label:Cadence (Folder 368, Box 5)
    - The Dudelsack Song, 1
    - Lonely Lips, 2
  - Bobby Christian, Record Label:Stepheny (Folder 369, Box 5)
    - English Toffee, 1
    - Jumpin Jack, 2
  - Lou Christie, Record Label:Roulette (Folder 370, Box 5)
    - Shy Boy, 1
    - It Can Happen, 2
  - Lou Christie, Record Label:MGM (Folder 371, Box 5)
    - Since I Don't Have You, 1
    - Wild Life's In Season, 2
  - Lou Christie, Record Label:Roulette (Folder 372, Box 5)
    - The Gypsy Cried, 1
    - Red Sails In The Sunset, 2
  - Eugene Church&The Fellows, Record Label:Class (Folder 373, Box 5)
    - Miami, 1
    - I Ain't Goin' For That, 2
  - Eugene Church&The Fellows, Record Label:Class (Folder 374, Box 5)
    - For The Rest Of My Life, 1
    - Pretty Girls Everywhere, 2
  - The Cineramas, Record Label:Rhapsody (Folder 375, Box 5)
    - Crying For You, 1
    - I'm Sorry Baby, 2
  - Jimmy Clanton, Record Label:Philips (Folder 376, Box 5)
    - Red Don't Go With Blue, 1
    - All The Words In The World, 2
  - Claudine Clark, Record Label:Chancellor (Folder 377, Box 5)
    - Who Will You Hurt, 1
    - Walk Me Home, 2
  - Claudine Clark, Record Label:Chancellor (Folder 378, Box 5)
    - Party Lights, 1
    - Disappointed, 2
  - Dave Clark Five, Record Label:Epic (Folder 379, Box 5)
    - I'll Be Yours (My Love), 1
    - Over and Over, 2
  - Dee Clark, Record Label:Abner (Folder 380, Box 5)
    - Cling A Ling, 1
    - At My Front Door, 2
  - Dee Clark, Record Label:Abner (Folder 381, Box 5)
    - Whispering Grass, 1
    - Just Keep It Up, 2
  - Dee Clark, Record Label:Abner (Folder 382, Box 5)
    - Hey Little Girl, 1
    - If It Wasn't For Love, 2
  - Dee Clark, Record Label:Abner (Folder 383, Box 5)
    - How About That, 1
    - Blues Get Off My Shoulder, 2
  - Dee Clark, Record Label:Vee-Jay (Folder 384, Box 5)
    - Raindrops, 1
    - I Want To Love You, 2
  - Petula Clark, Record Label:Warner Bros. (Folder 385, Box 5)
    - The Cat In The Window, 1
    - Fancy Dancin' Man, 2
  - Roy Clark, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 386, Box 5)
    - So Much To Remember, 1
    - Turn Around and Look Again, 2
  - The Classics, Record Label:Musicnote (Folder 387, Box 5)
    - Till Then, 1
    - Enie Minie Mo, 2
  - The Cleftones, Record Label:Gee (Folder 388, Box 5)
    - I Was Dreaming, 1
    - You Baby You, 2
  - The Cleftones, Record Label:Gee (Folder 389, Box 5)
    - Heart And Soul, 1
    - How Do You Feel, 2
  - The Cleftones, Record Label:Gee (Folder 390, Box 5)
    - Earth Angel, 1
    - Blues In The Night, 2
  - The Cleftones, Record Label:Gee (Folder 391, Box 5)
    - 'Deed I Do, 1
    - For Sentimental Reasons, 2
  - The Cleftones, Record Label:Gee (Folder 392, Box 5)
    - Neki-Hokey, 1
    - Can't We Be Sweethearts?, 2
  - The Cleftones, Record Label:Gee (Folder 393, Box 5)
    - Little Girl of Mine, 1
    - You're Driving Me Mad, 2
  - The Cleftones, Record Label:Gee (Folder 394, Box 5)
    - Happy Memories, 1
    - String Around My Heart, 2
  - The Cleftones, Record Label:Gee (Folder 395, Box 5)
    - Why You Do Me Like You Do, 1
    - I Like Your Style Of Making Love, 2
  - The Cleftones, Record Label:Gee (Folder 396, Box 5)
    - Trudy, 1
    - She's So Fine, 2
  - Clairette Clementino, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 397, Box 5)
    - Ev'rywhere, 1
    - See Me, 2
  - Buzz Clifford, Record Label:Columbia (Folder 398, Box 5)
    - Baby Sittin’ Boogie, 1
    - Driftwood, 2
  - Buzz Clifford, Record Label:Columbia (Folder 399, Box 5)
    - Simply Because, 1
    - Three Little Fishes, 2
  - Buzz Clifford, Record Label:Columbia (Folder 400, Box 5)
    - The Awakening, 1
    - I'll Never Forget, 2
  - The Climbers, Record Label:J&S (Folder 401, Box 5)
    - My Darlin' Dear, 1
    - Angels In Heaven Know I Love You, 2
  - Patsy Cline, Record Label:Decca (Folder 402, Box 5)
    - Strange, 1
    - She's Got You, 2
  - The Cluques, Record Label:Modern Hollywood (Folder 403, Box 5)
    - I Wanna Know Why, 1
    - The Girl In My Dreams, 2
  - The Clovers, Record Label:Atlantic (Folder 404, Box 5)
    - Good Lovin', 1
    - Here Goes A Fool, 2
  - The Clovers, Record Label:Atlantic (405, Box 6)
    - Hey, Doll Baby, 1
    - Devil or Angel, 2
  - The Clovers, Record Label:Atlantic (Folder 406, Box 6)
    - Your Tender Lips, 1
    - Love, Love, Love, 2
  - The Clovers, Record Label:Atlantic (Folder 407, Box 6)
    - You Good Looking Woman, 1
    - Here Comes Romance, 2
  - The Clovers, Record Label:Atlantic (Folder 408, Box 6)
    - Blue Velvet, 1
    - If You Love Me, 2
  - The Clovers, Record Label:Porwin (Folder 409, Box 6)
    - Stop Pretending, 1
    - One More Time (Come One), 2
  - The Clovers, Record Label:Rainbow (Folder 410, Box 6)
    - Yes Sir That's My Baby, 1
    - When You Come Back To Me, 2
  - The Clovers, Record Label:United Artists (Folder 411, Box 6)
    - Lovely, 1
    - One Mint Julep, 2
  - The Clovers, Record Label:United Artists (Folder 412, Box 6)
    - Stay Awhile, 1
    - Love Potion No. 9, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 413, Box 6)
    - Gee, Golly, 1
    - Dance!, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 414, Box 6)
    - Searchin', 1
    - Young Blood, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 415, Box 6)
    - Thumbin' A Ride, 1
    - Wait A Minute, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 416, Box 6)
    - That Is Rock And Roll, 1
    - Along Came Jones, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:2 copies Atco (Folder 417, Box 6)
    - Run Red Run, 1
    - What About Us, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 418, Box 6)
    - Poison Ivy, 1
    - I'm A Hog For You, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 419, Box 6)
    - Wake Me, Shake Me, 1
    - Stewball, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 420, Box 6)
    - Little Egypt, 1
    - Keep On Rolling, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 421, Box 6)
    - Brazil, 1
    - One Kiss Led To Another, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 422, Box 6)
    - My Baby Comes To Me, 1
    - Idol With The Golden Head, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 423, Box 6)
    - Shoppin' For Clothes, 1
    - The Snake And The Book Woman, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 424, Box 6)
    - Besame Mucho part 1, 1
    - Besame Mucho part 2, 2
  - The Coasters, Record Label:Atco (Folder 425, Box 6)
    - Girls Girls Girls part 1, 1
    - Girls Girls Girls part 2, 2
  - Eddie Cochran, Record Label:Liberty (Folder 426, Box 6)
    - Sittin' In The Balcony, 1
    - Dark Lonely Street, 2
  - Eddie Cochran, Record Label:Liberty (Folder 427, Box 6)
    - Don't Ever Let Me Go, 1
    - C'mon Everybody, 2
  - Nat "King" Cole, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 428, Box 6)
    - My Dream Sonata, 1
    - That's All There Is To That, 2
  - Nat "King" Cole, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 429, Box 6)
    - Mr. Wishing Well, 1
    - That Sunday, That Summer, 2
  - Nat "King" Cole, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 430, Box 6)
    - Looking Back, 1
    - Do I Like It, 2
  - Nat "King" Cole, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 431, Box 6)
    - China Gate, 1
    - When Rock and Roll Came to Trinidad, 2
  - Nat "King" Cole, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 432, Box 6)
    - Around The World, 1
    - Fascination, 2
    - An Affair To Remember, 3
    - There's A Gold Mine In The Sky, 4
  - The Collegians, Record Label:Winley (Folder 433, Box 6)
    - Zoom Zoom Zoom, 1
    - On Your Merry Way, 2
  - Carol Colins, Record Label:Dunes (Folder 434, Box 6)
    - Dear One, 1
    - Johnny, Oh Johnny, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (Folder 435, Box 6)
  - The Colts, Record Label:Vita (Folder 436, Box 6)
    - Adorable, 1
    - Lips Red As Wine, 2
  - The Colts, Record Label:Vita (Folder 437, Box 6)
    - Sweet Sixteen, 1
    - Honey Bun, 2
  - Perry Como With Mitchell Ayres And His Orchestra, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 438, Box 6)
    - Swinging Down The Lane, 1
    - South Of The Border, 2
    - Honey, Honey, 3
    - Angry, 4
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (Folder 439, Box 6)
  - Bobby Comstock, Record Label:Blaze (Folder 440, Box 6)
    - Sweet Talk, 1
    - Tennessee Waltz, 2
  - Bobby Comstock, Record Label:Jubilee (Folder 441, Box 6)
    - Bony Moronie, 1
    - Do That Little Thing, 2
  - The Concords, Record Label:Harlem (Folder 442, Box 6)
    - Monticello, 1
    - Candlelight, 2
  - The Conductor, Record Label:Jamie (Folder 443, Box 6)
    - Bla, Bla, Cha Cha Cha, 1
    - Pony Train, 2
  - The Continentals, Record Label:Port (Folder 444, Box 6)
    - Soft And Sweet, 1
    - Picture Of Love, 2
  - The Continental Four, Record Label:Jay Walking (Folder 445, Box 6)
    - What You Gave Up, 1
    - Day By Day, 2
  - L.C. Cooke, Record Label:Checker (Folder 446, Box 6)
    - Blue Tears, 1
    - Do You Remember, 2
  - L.C. Cooke, Record Label:Blue Rock (Folder 447, Box 6)
    - That's Where It's At, 1
    - Wonderful World, 2
  - Sam Cooke, Record Label:2 copies Keen (Folder 448, Box 6)
    - Summertime, 1
    - You Send Me, 2
  - Sam Cooke, Record Label:Keen (Folder 449, Box 6)
    - Desire Me, 1
    - For Sentimental Reasons, 2
  - Sam Cooke, Record Label:2 copies Keen (Folder 450, Box 6)
    - Only Sixteen, 1
    - Let's Go Steady Again, 2
  - Sam Cooke, Record Label:Keen (Folder 451, Box 6)
    - Blue Moon, 1
    - Love You Most Of All, 2
  - Sam Cooke, Record Label:Specialty (Folder 452, Box 6)
    - Happy In Love, 1
    - I Need You Now, 2
  - Sam Cooke, Record Label:Specialty (Folder 453, Box 6)
    - Forever, 1
    - I'll Come Running Back To You, 2
  - Sam Cooke, Record Label:Specialty (Folder 454, Box 6)
    - I Don't Want To Cry, 1
    - That's All I Need To Know, 2
  - Sam Cooke, Record Label:Keen (Folder 455, Box 6)
    - Along The Navajo Trail, 1
    - Wonderful World, 2
  - Sam Cooke, Record Label:Keen (Folder 456, Box 6)
    - Love Song From Houseboat, 1
    - Win Your Love For Me, 2
  - The Cookies, Record Label:Dimension (Folder 457, Box 6)
    - Stranger In My Arms, 1
    - Chains, 2
  - The Cookies, Record Label:Dimension (Folder 458, Box 6)
    - I Want A Boy For My Birthday, 1
    - Will Power, 2
  - The Cookies, Record Label:Dimension (Folder 459, Box 6)
    - Softly In The Night, 1
    - Don't Say Nothin’ Bad, 2
  - Eddie Cooley&The Dimples, Record Label:Royal Roost (Folder 460, Box 6)
    - Priscilla, 1
    - Got A Little Woman, 2
  - The Corsairs, Record Label:2 Copies Tuff (Folder 461, Box 6)
    - Thinkin', 1
    - Smokey Places, 2
  - Dave "Baby" Cortez, Record Label:Clock (Folder 462, Box 6)
    - Whispers, 1
    - Dave's Special, 2
  - Dave "Baby" Cortez, Record Label:Winley (Folder 463, Box 6)
    - Jammin' part 1, 1
    - Jammin' part 2, 2
  - Dave "Baby" Cortez, Record Label:Chess (Folder 464, Box 6)
    - Rinky Dink, 1
    - Getting Right, 2
  - The Corvairs, Record Label:Comet (Folder 465, Box 6)
    - Hey Sally Mae, 1
    - True True Love, 2
  - Don Costa, Record Label:Columbia (Folder 466, Box 6)
    - Flamenco Guitar, 1
    - Sugar Blues, 2
  - The Count Victors, Record Label:Coral (Folder 467, Box 6)
    - That's A Lie, 1
    - Old Acquaintance, 2
  - The Counts, Record Label:Dot (Folder 468, Box 6)
    - Hot Tamales, 1
    - Baby Don't You Know, 2
  - The C-Quins, Record Label:Chess (Folder 469, Box 6)
    - You've Been Crying, 1
    - My Only Love, 2
  - Floyd Cramer, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 470, Box 6)
    - Satan's Doll, 1
    - How High The Moon, 2
  - Floyd Cramer, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 471, Box 6)
    - For Those That Cry, 1
    - Hot Pepper, 2
  - Johnny Crawford, Record Label:Del-Fi (Folder 472, Box 6)
    - Donna, 1
    - Donna, 2
  - The Creators, Record Label:T-Kay (Folder 473, Box 6)
    - Boy He's Got It, 1
    - I'll Never Never Do It Again, 2
  - The Creatures, Record Label:Columbia (Folder 474, Box 6)
    - Turn Out The Light, 1
    - It Must Be Love, 2
  - Creedence Clearwater Revival, Record Label:Fantasy (Folder 475, Box 6)
    - Suzie Q (part I), 1
    - Suzie Q (part II), 2
  - The Crescendos, Record Label:Nasco (Folder 476, Box 6)
    - Oh Julie, 1
    - My Little Girl, 2
  - The Crests, Record Label:Coed (Folder 477, Box 6)
    - Beside You, 1
    - 16 Candles, 2
  - The Crests, Record Label:Coed (Folder 478, Box 6)
    - Paper Crown, 1
    - A Year Ago Today, 2
  - The Crests, Record Label:Coed (Folder 479, Box 6)
    - Step By Step, 1
    - Gee (But I'd Give The World), 2
  - The Crests, Record Label:Coed (Folder 480, Box 6)
    - I Thank The Moon, 1
    - Pretty Little Angel, 2
  - The Crests, Record Label:Coed (Folder 481, Box 6)
    - I Do, 1
    - Six Nights A Week, 2
  - The Crests, Record Label:2 Copies Coed (Folder 482, Box 6)
    - I Thank The Moon, 1
    - The Angels Listened In, 2
  - The Crests, Record Label:Coed (Folder 483, Box 6)
    - Flower Of Love, 1
    - Molly Mae, 2
  - The Crests, Record Label:Coed (Folder 484, Box 6)
    - Always You, 1
    - Trouble In Paradise, 2
  - The Crests, Record Label:Joyce (Folder 485, Box 6)
    - My Juanita, 1
    - Sweetest One, 2
  - The Crests, Record Label:Selma (Folder 486, Box 6)
    - Guilty, 1
    - Number One With Me, 2
  - The Crew-Cuts, Record Label:Whale (487, Box 7)
    - Twistin’ All Around The World, 1
    - Electric Chair, 2
  - The Crickets, Record Label:Beacon (Folder 488, Box 7)
    - Be Faithful, 1
    - Sleepy Little Cowboy, 2
  - The Crickets, Record Label:Brunswick (Folder 489, Box 7)
    - I'm Lookin’ For Someone To Love, 1
    - That'll Be The Day, 2
  - The Crickets, Record Label:Brunswick (Folder 490, Box 7)
    - Not Fade Away, 1
    - Oh, Boy, 2
  - The Critters, Record Label:Kapp (Folder 491, Box 7)
    - It Just Won't Be That Way, 1
    - Mr. Dieingly Sad, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (Folder 492, Box 7)
  - The Crowns, Record Label:R 'n B (Folder 493, Box 7)
    - Kiss And Make Up, 1
    - I'll Forget About You, 2
  - The Crows, Record Label:Rama (Folder 494, Box 7)
    - Baby Doll, 1
    - Sweet Sue, 2
  - Arthur "Big Boy" Crudup, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 495, Box 7)
    - Katie May, 1
    - Boyfriend Blues, 2
  - The Cruisers, Record Label:V-Tone (Folder 496, Box 7)
    - If I Knew, 1
    - Miss Fine, 2
  - The Crystals, Record Label:Deluxe (Folder 497, Box 7)
    - My Girl, 1
    - God Only Knows, 2
  - The Crystals, Record Label:Philles (Folder 498, Box 7)
    - He's A Rebel, 1
    - I Love You Eddie, 2
  - The Cues, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 499, Box 7)
    - Charlie Brown, 1
    - Charlie Brown, 2
  - The Cues, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 500, Box 7)
    - Oh My Darlin', 1
    - Burn That Candle, 2
  - The Cues, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 501, Box 7)
    - Why, 1
    - Prince Or Pauper, 2
  - The Cuff Links, Record Label:Dooto (Folder 502, Box 7)
    - My Heart, 1
    - Guided Missiles, 2
  - The Cuff Links, Record Label:Dooto (Folder 503, Box 7)
    - The Winner, 1
    - How You Lied, 2
  - The Cupids, Record Label:Decca (Folder 504, Box 7)
    - My Dog Likes Your Dog, 1
    - The Answer To Your Prayers, 2
  - The Cupids, Record Label:KC (Folder 505, Box 7)
    - Brenda, 1
    - For You, 2
  - Earl Curry&The Blenders, Record Label:R and B (Folder 506, Box 7)
    - Late Rising Moon, 1
    - I Want To Be With You, 2
  - King Curtis, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 507, Box 7)
    - Strollin' Home, 1
    - Mess Around, 2
  - Johnny Cymbal, Record Label:Kapp (Folder 508, Box 7)
    - Mr. Bass Man, 1
    - Sacred Lovers Vow, 2
  - Daddy Cool, Record Label:Reprise (Folder 509, Box 7)
    - I'll Never Smile Again, 1
    - I'll Never Smile Again, 2
  - Dakota Station, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 510, Box 7)
    - No Mama - No Papa, 1
    - For The Rest Of My Life, 2
  - Dakota Station, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 511, Box 7)
    - I Told You So, 1
    - You Know I Do, 2
  - Dakota Station, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 512, Box 7)
    - My Friend, 1
    - Don't Mean Maybe, 2
  - Dakota Station, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 513, Box 7)
    - My Heart's Delight, 1
    - What Do You Know About Love, 2
  - Dale And Grace, Record Label:Montel (Folder 514, Box 7)
    - Stop And Think It Over, 1
    - Bad Luck, 2
  - Dale And Grace, Record Label:Montel (Folder 515, Box 7)
    - What Am I Living For?, 1
    - Something Special, 2
  - Vic Dana, Record Label:Dolton (Folder 516, Box 7)
    - Distant Drums, 1
    - Distant Drums, 2
  - The Danderliers, Record Label:States (Folder 517, Box 7)
    - Little Man, 1
    - May God Be With You, 2
  - The Dandevilles, Record Label:Guyden (Folder 518, Box 7)
    - Nasty Breaks, 1
    - There's A Reason, 2
  - Johnny Dankworth, Record Label:Roulette (Folder 519, Box 7)
    - African Waltz, 1
    - Moanin', 2
  - The Danleers, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 520, Box 7)
    - I Really Love You, 1
    - My Flaming Heart, 2
  - The Danleers, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 521, Box 7)
    - One Summer Night, 1
    - Wheelin' And A-Dealin', 2
  - Danny And The Juniors, Record Label:ABC Paramount (Folder 522, Box 7)
    - Dottie, 1
    - In The Meantime, 2
  - Danny And The Juniors, Record Label:ABC Paramount (Folder 523, Box 7)
    - Schoolboy Romance, 1
    - Rock and Roll Is Here To Stay, 2
  - Danny And The Juniors, Record Label:2 Copies Swan (Folder 524, Box 7)
    - Twistin' U.S.A., 1
    - A Thousand Miles Away, 2
  - Danny And The Juniors, Record Label:Swan (Folder 525, Box 7)
    - Daydreamer, 1
    - Pony Express, 2
  - The Dappers, Record Label:Foxie (Folder 526, Box 7)
    - Chicken Twist, 1
    - Lonely Street, 2
  - The Dappers, Record Label:Peacock (Folder 527, Box 7)
    - Mambo Oongh, 1
    - Come Back To Me, 2
  - Bobby Darin, Record Label:Atco (Folder 528, Box 7)
    - Plain Jane, 1
    - While I'm Gone, 2
  - Bobby Darin, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 529, Box 7)
    - You're The Reason I'm Living, 1
    - Now You're Gone, 2
  - Bobby Darin, Record Label:Atco (Folder 530, Box 7)
    - What'd I Say (part 1), 1
    - What'd I Say (part 2), 2
  - Bobby Darin, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 531, Box 7)
    - I Wonder Who’s Kissing Her Now, 1
    - As Long as I'm Singing, 2
  - James Darren, Record Label:Colpix (Folder 532, Box 7)
    - Conscience, 1
    - Dream Big, 2
  - James Darren, Record Label:Colpix (Folder 533, Box 7)
    - Blame It On My Youth, 1
    - They Should Have Given You The Oscar, 2
  - Sammy Davis Jr., Record Label:Reprise (Folder 534, Box 7)
    - The Shelter Of Your Arms, 1
    - This Was My Love, 2
  - The Dawns, Record Label:Climax (Folder 535, Box 7)
    - How Deep Is The Ocean, 1
    - Why Did You Let Me Love You, 2
  - Bobby Day, Record Label:Class (Folder 536, Box 7)
    - Say Yes, 1
    - That's All I Want, 2
  - Bobby Day, Record Label:Class (Folder 537, Box 7)
    - I Don't Want To, 1
    - My Blue Heaven, 2
  - Johnny Day, Record Label:Blue Star (Folder 538, Box 7)
    - One Of These Days, 1
    - I'll Keep On Loving You, 2
  - Johnny Dee, Record Label:Colonial (Folder 539, Box 7)
    - Sittin' In The Balcony, 1
    - A-Plus In Love, 2
  - Mercy Dee, Record Label:Specialty (Folder 540, Box 7)
    - Get To Gettin', 1
    - Dark Muddy Bottom, 2
  - Deep River Boys, Record Label:Vik (Folder 541, Box 7)
    - Whole Wide World, 1
    - All My Love Belongs To You, 2
  - Dee-Vines, Record Label:Relic (Folder 542, Box 7)
    - I Believe, 1
    - World's Greatest Lover, 2
  - Del-Lourds, Record Label:Solar (Folder 543, Box 7)
    - Alone, 1
    - All Alone, 2
  - The Dells, Record Label:Cadet (Folder 544, Box 7)
    - Believe Me, 1
    - Oh, What A Night, 2
  - The Dells, Record Label:Oldies (Folder 545, Box 7)
    - Oh What A Nite, 1
    - I Wanna Go Home, 2
  - The Dells, Record Label:Vee-Jay (Folder 546, Box 7)
    - Jo-Jo, 1
    - Oh What A Nite, 2
  - The Dells, Record Label:Vee-Jay (Folder 547, Box 7)
    - The Springer, 1
    - What You Say Baby, 2
  - The Dells, Record Label:Vee-Jay (Folder 548, Box 7)
    - Why Do You Have To Go, 1
    - Dance, Dance, Dance, 2
  - Eddie Delmar, Record Label:Madison (Folder 549, Box 7)
    - Blanche, 1
    - Love Bells, 2
  - The Delmonicos, Record Label:Musictone (Folder 550, Box 7)
    - Until You, 1
    - The World's Biggest Fool, 2
  - The Del-Satins, Record Label:Laurie (Folder 551, Box 7)
    - Teardrops Follow Me, 1
    - Best Wishes, Good Luck, Good-Bye, 2
  - The Del-Stars, Record Label:Mellomood (Folder 552, Box 7)
    - Why Do You Have To Go?, 1
    - Who Said You Wasn't Mine, 2
  - The Deltairs, Record Label:Felsted (Folder 553, Box 7)
    - You Won't Be Satisfied, 1
    - Who Would Have Thought It, 2
  - The Deltairs, Record Label:Ivy (Folder 554, Box 7)
    - Lullaby Of The Bells, 1
    - It's Only You, Dear, 2
  - Delta Rhythm Boys, Record Label:Decca (Folder 555, Box 7)
    - Shoes, 1
    - Kiss Crazy Baby, 2
  - The Deltas, Record Label:Gone (Folder 556, Box 7)
    - Lamplight, 1
    - Let Me Share Your Dream, 2
  - The Del Vikings, Record Label:ABC Paramount (Folder 557, Box 7)
    - Bring Back Your Heart, 1
    - I'll Never Stop Crying, 2
  - The Del Vikings, Record Label:Dot (Folder 558, Box 7)
    - Come Go With Me, 1
    - How Can I Find True Love, 2
  - The Del Vikings, Record Label:2 Copies Dot (Folder 559, Box 7)
    - Little Billy Boy, 1
    - What Made Maggie Run, 2
  - The Del Vikings, Record Label:Dot (Folder 560, Box 7)
    - Little Billy Boy, 1
    - What Made Maggie Run, 2
  - The Del Vikings, Record Label:Gateway (Folder 561, Box 7)
    - We Three, 1
    - I've Got To Know, 2
  - The Del Vikings, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 562, Box 7)
    - What'cha Gotta Lose, 1
    - Come Along With Me, 2
  - The Del Vikings, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 563, Box 7)
    - Cool Shake, 1
    - Jitterbug Mary, 2
  - The Del Vikings, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 564, Box 7)
    - Snowbound, 1
    - Your Book Of Life, 2
  - The Del Vikings, Record Label:Ship (Folder 565, Box 7)
    - Over The Rainbow, 1
    - A Sunday Kind Of Love, 2
  - The Del Vikings, Record Label:Fee Bee (Folder 566, Box 7)
    - Whispering Bells, 1
    - Come Go With Me, 2
  - The Demensions, Record Label:Mohawk (Folder 567, Box 7)
    - Nursery Rhime Rock, 1
    - Over The Rainbow, 2
  - The Desires, Record Label:Hull (Folder 568, Box 7)
    - Hey Lena, 1
    - Let It Please Be You, 2
  - The Desires, Record Label:Hull (Folder 569, Box 7)
    - Rendezvous With You, 1
    - Set Me Free (My Darling), 2
  - The Devotions, Record Label:Roulette 2 copies (570, Box 8)
    - Rip Van Winkle, 1
    - (I Love You) For Sentimental Reasons, 2
  - The Diablos, Record Label:Fortune (Folder 571, Box 8)
    - The Wind, 1
    - Baby, Be Mine, 2
  - The Diablos, Record Label:Fortune (Folder 572, Box 8)
    - Jump, Shake, and Move, 1
    - The Way You Dog Me Around, 2
  - The Dials, Record Label:Hilltop (Folder 573, Box 8)
    - No Hard Feelings, 1
    - Win Yourself A Lover, 2
  - The Diamonds, Record Label:Atlantic (Folder 574, Box 8)
    - Romance In The Dark, 1
    - Cherry, 2
  - The Diamonds, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 575, Box 8)
    - The Stroll, 1
    - Land Of Beauty, 2
  - The Diamonds, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 576, Box 8)
    - Faithful and True, 1
    - Little Darlin', 2
  - The Diamonds, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 577, Box 8)
    - Eternal Lovers, 1
    - Walking Along, 2
  - Dick And Deedee, Record Label:Warner Bros. (Folder 578, Box 8)
    - Just ‘Round The River Bend, 1
    - Thou Shalt Not Steal, 2
  - Bo Diddley, Record Label:Checker (Folder 579, Box 8)
    - Mona, 1
    - Hey! Bo Diddley, 2
  - Bo Diddley, Record Label:Checker (Folder 580, Box 8)
    - Aztec, 1